(Leonard:)How about the toaster oven?
(Sheldon:)What did the toaster oven ever do to you?
What did I do to Jimmy Mullins
in the third grade?
(Leonard:)He still punched me in the face
with my own fists.
(Leonard:)Sorry, you little nerd. You were just
in the wrong boys' room at the wrong time.
(Howard:)Gentlemen, goggles.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, this is an auspicious moment.
(Sheldon:)Like Robert Oppenheimer
or Neil Armstrong...
(Sheldon:)...we need the appropriate words
to mark this historic scientific event.
How about, "Die, toaster, die"?
(Leonard:)That'll do it.
(Raj(after watching complete destruction of toaster oven):)All right, what's next?
No, I think I'm just gonna stay in tonight
and do laundry.
[SCREAMS]